https://www.hitxp.com/privacy-policy/

ReadArticlesEconomicsEntertainmentHistoryLogicPoliticsSci-TechSocietySoftwarePoemsSeeImagesPhotographyQuotesLearnCodeSanskrit LessonsMusic NotationsMusic ArticlesKannada SongsTamil SongsHindi SongsEnglish SongsTelugu SongsTunes of CommercialsPatriotic SongsNursery RhymesListenMusicUseDictionaryLyricsToolsVirtual PianoWho?Contact
Sign in
Welcome!Log into your accountyour usernameyour password
Forgot your password?Privacy Policy
Password recoveryRecover your passwordyour email
Search
Sign inWelcome! Log into your accountyour usernameyour password Forgot your password? Get helpPrivacy PolicyPassword recoveryRecover your passwordyour email A password will be e-mailed to you.
HitXP
ReadArticlesEconomicsEntertainmentHistoryLogicPoliticsSci-TechSocietySoftwarePoemsSeeImagesPhotographyQuotesLearnCodeSanskrit LessonsMusic NotationsMusic ArticlesKannada SongsTamil SongsHindi SongsEnglish SongsTelugu SongsTunes of CommercialsPatriotic SongsNursery RhymesListenMusicUseDictionaryLyricsToolsVirtual PianoWho?Contact
Home
Privacy Policy Privacy PolicyYour privacy is critically important to us.At HitXP we have a few fundamental principles:We don’t ask you for personal information unless we truly need it. (We can’t stand services that ask you for things like your gender or income level for no apparent reason.)We don’t share your personal information with anyone except to comply with the law, develop our products, or protect our rights.We don’t store personal information on our servers unless required for the on-going operation of one of our services.Below is our privacy policy which incorporates these goals:Website VisitorsLike most website operators, HitXP collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. HitXP’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how HitXP’s visitors use its website. From time to time, HitXP may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.HitXP also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses. HitXP does not use such information to identify its visitors, however, and does not disclose such information, other than under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information, as described below.Gathering of Personally-Identifying InformationCertain visitors to HitXP choose to interact with HitXP in ways that require HitXP to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that HitXP gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who post comments at HitXP to provide their name and email address. In such cases, HitXP collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with HitXP. HitXP does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.Aggregated StatisticsHitXP may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. For instance, HitXP may monitor the most popular blogs on the website or use spam screened by the Akismet service to help identify spam. HitXP may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, HitXP does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying InformationHitXP discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those organizations that(i) need to know that information in order to process it on HitXP’s behalf or to provide services available at HitXP, and(ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others.Some of those organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using HitXP, you consent to the transfer of such information to them.HitXP will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to organizations, as described above, HitXP discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only when required to do so by law, or when HitXP believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of HitXP, third parties or the public at large. If you have supplied your email address to HitXP, HitXP may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with HitXP. We primarily use our website to communicate this type of information, so we expect to keep this type of email to a minimum. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. HitXP takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.CookiesA cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. HitXP uses cookies to help HitXP identify and track visitors, their usage of HitXP website, and their website access preferences. HitXP visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using HitXP’s websites, with the drawback that certain features of HitXP’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.Ads Ads appearing on any of our websites may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by HitXP and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.Comments Comments and other content submitted to the Akismet anti-spam service are not saved on their servers unless they were marked as false positives, in which case they would be stored long enough to use them to improve the service to avoid future false positives.Privacy Policy Changes Although most changes are likely to be minor, HitXP may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in HitXP’s sole discretion. HitXP encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.Download HitXP Mobile App on Google PlayFacebookLikeInstagramFollowPinterestFollowRSS FeedSubscribeSound CloudFollowTwitterFollowYoutubeSubscribe Download HitXP on Google PlaySubscribe to HitXP Articles
Subscribe to HitXP Music
MUST READThe difference between Itihasa and Puranas
August 5, 2020 0 Online Education should be interactive and innovative – Fun to Learn June 11, 2020The Complete List of Dhatus – Sanskrit Root Words and their English meaning April 16, 2020Sanskrit Lesson 4 – Word Creation Magic using Dhatus April 15, 2020The Secret Role of Karma in Mahabharata April 10, 2020 LATEST MUSIC NOTATIONSSo Gaya Ye Jahan – Tezaab – Piano Notations
June 8, 2020 0 Background Theme (BGM) – Mouna Ragam – Piano Notations June 3, 2020Dil Kya Kare Jab Kisi Se – Julie – Piano Notations June 3, 2020Albela Sajan Aayo Re – Hum Dil De Chuke Sanam – Piano Notations May 30, 2020Chinni Chinni Aasa Chinnadaani Asa – Roja – Piano Notations May 30, 2020
Facebook
Instagram
Pinterest
Soundcloud
Twitter
Youtube
Terms of UsePrivacy PolicyCopyright Policy © 2003-2020 Gurudev
